export const MOCKED_EXERCISES_RESPONSE = {
	exercises: [
		{
			id: "ex_01",
			type: "single_choice",
			question: "I <b>___</b> finished debugging the main function; it works perfectly now.",
			correctAnswer: "have just finished",
			options: ["just finished", "have just finished", "had just finished"],
		},
		{
			id: "ex_02",
			type: "single_choice",
			question: "She <b>___</b> worked on this project <i>since</i> last March.",
			correctAnswer: "has worked",
			options: ["has worked", "worked", "is working"],
		},
		{
			id: "ex_03",
			type: "single_choice",
			question: "My team <b>___</b> never <i>lost</i> a match on this map.",
			correctAnswer: "has never lost",
			options: ["has never lost", "never lost", "had never lost"],
		},
		{
			id: "ex_04",
			type: "single_choice",
			question: "Where <b>___</b> you <b>___</b> your new keyboard? I don't see it.",
			correctAnswer: "have you put",
			options: ["have you put", "did you put", "have you been putting"],
		},
		{
			id: "ex_05",
			type: "single_choice",
			question: "The server <b>___</b> completely <b>___</b> down. We need to restart it.",
			correctAnswer: "has completely shut",
			options: ["has completely shut", "completely shut", "is completely shutting"],
		},
		{
			id: "ex_06",
			type: "single_choice",
			question: "I <b>___</b> <i>known</i> him <i>since</i> we started working together.",
			correctAnswer: "have known",
			options: ["have known", "knew", "know"],
		},
		{
			id: "ex_07",
			type: "single_choice",
			question: "<b>___</b> you <b>___</b> the new patch <i>yet</i>?",
			correctAnswer: "Have you installed",
			options: ["Have you installed", "Did you install", "Are you installing"],
		},
		{
			id: "ex_08",
			type: "single_choice",
			question: "He <b>___</b> <i>read</i> all the documentation for this API.",
			correctAnswer: "has read",
			options: ["has read", "read", "reads"],
		},
		{
			id: "ex_09",
			type: "fill_in_blank",
			question:
				"My boss <b>___</b> (not / approve) the request for the new hardware yet. (Use Present Perfect Simple)",
			correctAnswer: "has not approved|hasn't approved",
		},
		{
			id: "ex_10",
			type: "fill_in_blank",
			question:
				"We <b>___</b> (live) in this city for ten years. (Use Present Perfect Simple)",
			correctAnswer: "have lived",
		},
		{
			id: "ex_11",
			type: "fill_in_blank",
			question:
				"The game <b>___</b> (just / start), so you haven't missed much. (Use Present Perfect Simple)",
			correctAnswer: "has just started",
		},
		{
			id: "ex_12",
			type: "fill_in_blank",
			question:
				"How many times <b>___</b> (you / win) a ranked match this week? (Use Present Perfect Simple)",
			correctAnswer: "have you won",
		},
		{
			id: "ex_13",
			type: "fill_in_blank",
			question:
				"I <b>___</b> (never / play) a more exciting strategy game. (Use Present Perfect Simple)",
			correctAnswer: "have never played",
		},
	],
};
